Here is how I automated my morning routine
all of it runs while I am still hitting snooze
First, a script pulls my calendar and to-do list
then it picks the three things that actually matter today
It fires off a smart-plug command
so my coffee starts brewing five minutes before I even walk into the kitchen
Then it records a 30-second voice note summarizing my day
and sends it to my own messaging app
Three small automations
That is it
But it saves me 20 minutes every single morning
I used to wake up already behind
Now I wake up caught up
The whole thing is a 40-line script
I will link it in the comments if you want to try it
Seriously go automate one thing this weekend
Future you will be annoyed you did not do it sooner